Hello hi friends I am Jitendra and
welcome you to the channel details of Gaadi Aapka Free.
Friends the name of the city we are going to talk about today
is RBL Bank
Limited. Friends if you are
enrolled in IDBI Bank Limited, this is your
eggplant in your body, then
listen carefully to what I am going to tell you today. So
friends as you must have noticed today
that despite the market falling today,
RBL Bank rose by ₹1 today
and the same thing is being seen in Bandhan Bank for a
long time, so
friends today we will know what is the reason behind this,
friends as you know both the quarters of RBL Bank were
not good while shaking inside both, your
IDBI Bank which the
company
subscribed
in the last series, the profit was 140 crores
remained at Jyothi Chhattisgarh, along with
bank jobs in this way, after that friends
if you are not able to understand that
despite being subscribed, there was a
rise despite the fall and the market falling in it, then
friends
in this video I request you so
friends if you
will watch the video  So in this you will see
a pattern of long in pregnancy which
can take it to 297 grh
grh
subscribe was
subscribed
but in this drink the share office went up
then that will be the only reason so
Raghava has seen it falling
subscribe in it friends if you have
subscribed to this channel of his
which is standing on the price of the share which was running in the market except Thursday, very positive in your topic friends, then I
agree that if this share
goes up then you
can see it going up to ₹300 or even ₹100, you can
get more profit in this second I
can subscribe
to 270 subscribe
and if you
subscribe
now you have seen that this
subscribe will
tell you this use
friends if you have long term and you are
already invested then your
stoploss will be 155 friends if the
level below 125 is greased then you
can see it in lower levels,
stoploss will be 155 and
Subscribe was also Juhi and did 227, the
level can also come above that,
subscribe, if you can make this recipe in this, then to
subscribe, subscribe
and this
means comment and subscribe, stay
away, keep moving your juice topics upwards,
what happens with this is your step
follow, at the
time of production, whatever position you are in
in the area, your
positive profit is yours,
friends, now you have seen and
subscribe, if you drink and
support this, then you
subscribe, today's short term target,
I have told you your stoploss,
if you think that you
cannot do that because of this and if you do something like this,
you can use it as a share, like, subscribe,
now
you can use it at both the times, so
friends, if you liked the information given by me, then
please subscribe to my channel,
like the video
[music]
subscribe to